bigworldsports.com 2017-05-09

# Bigworldsports | Privacy.

### Privacy

What information do we collect? The privacy of our visitors to this site is of extreme importance to us. We allow third-party advertising companies (like Google Adsense) to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google�s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. Please note that these companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers� respective websites.. What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: ; To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) ; To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) ; To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) ; To process transactions Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. Terms and Conditions Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://livefootballvideo.net Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. http:bigworldsports.com wosoccer2(@)gmail (dot)com - This document was last modified on 03.05.2017 About Us livefootballvideo.net | Live Football streaming, football highlights and full matches. If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. http://www.bigworldsports.com wosoccer2(@)gmail (dot)com
